// Array containing questions


// Qs source: https://www.proprofs.com/quiz-school/story.php?title=compro_12zi
var quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "HTML stands for HyperText __________ Language."
        options: ["Market", "Marker", "Markup", "Marking"]
        answer: "Markup"
    } {
        question: "Texts that are enclosed on a <title> tag are all displayed in which part of the browser?"
        options: ["Title Bar", "Tab", "Menu Bar", "Tool Bar"]
        answer: "Title Bar"
    } {
        question: "These are the basic units or building blocks of an HTML file."
        options: ["Tag", "HTTP", "Value", "Attribute"]
        answer: "Tag"
    } {
        question: "Tags that cannot stand alone are called…"
        options: ["Empty Tag", "Markup Tag", "Container Tag", "Standalone Tag"]
        answer: "Container Tag"
    } {
        question: "_________ are used to provide additional information about the tag and go in name-value pairs separated by an equal sign ="
        options: ["HTTPs", "Values", "Tags", "Attributes"]
        answer: "Attributes"
    } {
        question: "A(n) ________ is an assigned property to an attribute."
        options: ["HTTP", "Value", "Tag", "Attribute"]
        answer: "Value"
    } {
        question: "HTML files are divided into 2 parts: the head and the __________"
        options: ["Attribute", "Body", "Title", "HTML"]
        answer: "Body"
    } {
        question: "Everything that appears on your webpage may it be texts, images, videos and others should then be put on the body which is enclosed in…"
        options: ["<head>", "<title>", "<body>", "<html>"]
        answer: "<body>"
    } {
        question: "This attribute can be used under the declaration of the <body> tag if you want to add a background image on the web page."
        options: ["background", "bgcolor", "text", "link"]
        answer: "background"
    } {
        question: "This attribute can be used under the declaration of the <body> tag if you want to customize the background color of your webpage."
        options: ["background", "bgcolor", "text", "link"]
        answer: "bgcolor"
    } {
        question: "This attribute can be used under the declaration of the <body> tag if you want to change the color of all the hyperlinks in the webpage"
        options: ["background", "bgcolor", "text", "link"]
        answer: "link"
    } {
        question: "Which among the heading levels is the smallest font size?"
        options: ["h1", "h3", "h5", "h6"]
        answer: "h6"
    } {
        question: "This attribute indicates the position of the text within an object."
        options: ["align", "left", "center", "right"]
        answer: "align"
    } {
        question: "This tag is used to create paragraphs."
        options: ["hr", "p", "ol", "br"]
        answer: "p"
    } {
        question: "This type of list enumerates each item in a bulleted form."
        options: ["dl", "li", "ul", "dt"]
        answer: "li"
    }







]